# Kenji Mau

## Front End Developer

#### SUMMARY

Versatile Front End Developer with 8+ years of experience focused on writing clean & efficient code to build responsive, effective and userfriendly websites. Self motivated leader and a fast learner with a passion for design. Areas of expertise include Wordpress driven websites, HTML5, CSS3, and custom theme development.

#### SKILLS

#### Coding

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Sass, jQuery, Basic GSAP, Basic Git/Version Control, PHP, Wordpress, Drupal, Wireframing/Prototyping, Bootstrap, Foundation

## Design & Software

Sketch, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Apple Productivity Suite and Microsoft Office

#### CONTACT

3810 Redding St. #6, Oakland, CA 94619

T: (205) 478 8547 E: krm218@gmail.com WWW.KENMAU.COM

## LANGUAGES

Fluent in written and verbal **Spanish** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Jun 2017 - Jan 2020

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

#### WHM Creative Oakland, CA

- responsible for both back-end and front-end development, across multiple environments and project types, including Wordpress themes and email templates
- creation of email templates, banner ads, websites and interactive HTML info graphics
- coding and QA (using Litmus) of email templates to be compatible with all clients
- designing and implementing new site features and functionality
- establishing and guiding a website's architecture
- ensuring high-performance and availability, and managing all technical aspects of the CMS
- helping to formulate effective, responsive designs and turning them into working themes or functional templates
- Projects include softbankrobotics.com/us, prcsf.org, bospar.com, whmcreative.com, sparklecut.com, orig3n.com

May 2015 - Jun 2017

## WEB DEVELOPER

## Sidecar Agency Berkeley, CA

- Programming of web pages, sites and other related assets based on web standards
- Ensure adherence to provided creative designs and technical requirements
- Utilize a working knowledge of current JavaScript libraries, library plugins, frameworks, etc.
- Troubleshoot, identify and fix bugs in own code; assist in overall QA process for the department
- Projects include pier39.com, centralcoast-tourism.com, 24hoursoflemons.com

Jan 2014 - April 2015

#### INTERACTIVE WEB DESIGNER

## Better World Advertising San Francisco, CA

- Create interactive and responsive web design for a variety of social marketing campaigns that reach audiences nationally and internationally.
- Design, develop, wireframe, code, implement, and maintain websites utilizing CMS systems such as Drupal and Wordpress.

Aug 2012 - Present

## FRONT END DEVELOPER

## Independent Consultant

- Design and develop websites that are userfriendly, effective, responsive, mobile-friendly, cross-browser compliant and appealing
- Implement end-to-end custom Drupal and Wordpress sites

#### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly, 2014
Front End Web Development

Mississippi State University, 2012 B.B.A. in International Business and Marketing B.A. in Foreign Language, Spanish